

## **Gysbert Lucas Olivier**

Software Craftsman

Last update: Tue May 08 2018 20:46:54 GMT+0200 (South Africa Standard Time)
The online version is available at

<a href="http://LucasScript.github.io/my-cv-repo">http://LucasScript.github.io/my-cv-repo</a>

## Profile

I have more than 4 years' employment experience in software development. From June 2017 I entered a roll where I developed mainly in a full stack environment. Prior to this I was in a roll where I developed in a Java environment.

My time working in the financial industry has taught me a lot as I improved legacy and built new features to assist the business to grow in providing better client experience.

I like to see myself not just as a developer but as a software craftsman that code by principles that improve the current and empowers the future.

When I'am not coding I enjoy cycling, photography and gaming.

## **Employment**

#### Software Developer at Investec

January 2014 - Present

Worked 3+ years on Java/Xml base system. I subsequently moved into a fullstack angular and node is environment.

#### Intern Developer at FOXit (Pty) Ltd

November 2012 - December 2012

As a holiday job I worked as an unpaid intern and developed a basic Windows 8 application.

#### **Project Assistant** at Scadco

July 2011 - July 2011

During holidays I assisted in setting up computers and systems in schools.

#### **Education**

# Honors Bachelor of Science(BSc) in Computer Science and Information Systems at North-West University

2013

My year project was on Navigation with Augmented and Virtual Reality. I developed an Android Application for a proof of concept.

This degree's subjects were focused on SQL databases, computer security and image processing.

## **Bachelor of Science(BSc) in Information Technology** at North-West University

2010 - 2012

This degree's subjects were focused on JAVA and C# languages, and some business focused subjects.

### National senior certificate at High School Ben Vorster

2005 - 2009

Subjects included: Afrikaans, English, Mathematics, Life Orientation, Engineering Graphics and Design, Information Technology and Physical science

### References

Available on request

DETAILS Sandton, 2191, South Africa +27718951225

lucasoli4@gmail.com

DATE/PLACE OF BIRTH 1991-01-30 / South Africa

NATIONALITY South African

**GITHUB LINKEDIN** 

LANGUAGES English

Afrikaans

SKILLS Team work Communication

TECH Java, XML, SQL

HTML, CSS, SCSS

JavaScript, TypeScript

Node.js, Angular.js

**Bootstrap** 

HOBBIES Cycling Photography Arduino Projects